

### CONTACT

- +254-725-406-004
- Nairobi, Kenya
- https://aogajoseph.github.i o/Personal-Website/

### **EDUCATION**

### 2018 - Present ZERO TO MASTERY ACADEMY

Certificate, Full-stack
JavaScript

**April**, 2008

# INTRO-TECH COMPUTER COLLEGE

• Certificate in IT

### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React
- NPM
- Github

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Creativity
- Time Management
- Teamwork
- Adaptability

# **JOSEPH ONYANGO**

WEB DEVELOPER, DESIGNER & DIGITAL ARTIST

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a versatile professional specializing in web development, web design, and digital art. I combine my technical skills with artistic creativity to craft user-friendly websites and applications that are both visually appealing and highly functional. By seamlessly integrating aesthetics with technology, I strive to deliver digital solutions that not only meet the needs of users but also stand out in the competitive tech landscape.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Zero to Mastery Academy**

Volunteer, Web Developer

2018 - PRESENT

- Collaborates with academy members in completing coding challenges.
- · Performing coding tasks.
- · Contributing to open-source projects.

# Spina-bifida & Hydrocephalus Association of Kenya (SHAK)

2020- 2023

Web Developer

Built and designed websites and user interfaces and digital media with stunning visual appeal, robust functionality and user-friendly experiences.

### **FUTURE LEARNING TRACKS**

- Advanced JavaScript.
- NodeJS for Back-end development.
- SQL and NoSQL Databases.
- CI/CD Pipelines and Automation.
- · Al and Machine Learning.
- Advanced Cloud Computing.
- · Design Thinking.
- · Technopreneurship.